<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollingText</string>
    <string name="article_title">Android Intercept</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Brian &amp; Charles</string>
    <string name="article_text">
        <b>Brian</b>\n
        Brian Pulfer (Switzerland, 21.09.1995) is a computer scientist that recently obtained his
        bachelor degree from SUPSI (<i>Scuola Universitaria Professionale della Svizzera Italiana</i>)
         located in Manno.\n\n

        He graduated with a bachelor thesis work about a classifier to disambiguate ambiguous scientific article authors.\n
        Ever since first studying data science and artificial intelligence, Brian was fascinated
        by the powerful tools that few math could bring to humanity.\n
        That\'s the reason why he\'s following a master course in Artificial Intelligence at \'USI\'
        (<i>Università della Svizzera Italiana</i>)\n\n

        Apart from computer science related topics, Brian is very passionate about sports. In fact,
        he has been playing football in a team from when he was 16 to when he was 21, and has been frequenting
         the gym for the last 3 years. He spends most of his free time doing physical activities, studying or
         playing video-games.\n\n

        Friends of him says that he\'s funny, loyal, smart and <b>very determined</b>.\n\n

        He\'s now a member of the \'<b>Android Intercept</b>\'.\n\n\n\n



        <b>Charles</b>\n
        My name is Charles and I am one of the team \'Android Intercept\'.  It was triangle before but now we only got two people.\n\n

        I am from China but I spent my college life in the U. S.  and that is where I got the accent.
        I lived in LA during that time in the past and I spent the last year in Shanghai. Both of them are big, if not too big , big cities.
        So, I am really looking forward to living in Lugano for next two years.
        And I would love to spend some time exploring Switzerland and Europe.

    </string>


</resources>
